List<Map<String, dynamic>> partFiveQuestions = [
  {
    'question':
    'In pressure-regulated volume control (PRVC) ventilation, what does the ventilator adjust to deliver a set tidal volume?',
    'answers': [
      'Inspiratory pressure',
      'Respiratory rate',
      'Inspiratory time',
      'Expiratory time',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What term describes the condition in which a patient initiates a breath, but the ventilator does not provide any support?',
    'answers': [
      'Asynchronous ventilation',
      'Auto-triggering',
      'Synchronized ventilation',
      'Spontaneous ventilation',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which type of mechanical ventilation mode allows the patient to determine the respiratory rate and tidal volume?',
    'answers': [
      'Pressure control ventilation',
      'Assist-control ventilation',
      'SIMV ventilation',
      'Pressure support ventilation',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'When using a high-frequency oscillatory ventilator (HFOV), what parameter is primarily adjusted to control ventilation?',
    'answers': [
      'Tidal volume',
      'Frequency (Hz)',
      'Inspiratory pressure',
      'FiO2',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which ventilator mode is typically used for patients with acute respiratory failure when there is concern about high peak inspiratory pressures?',
    'answers': [
      'Pressure support ventilation',
      'Pressure control ventilation',
      'Volume control ventilation',
      'Bilevel positive airway pressure (BiPAP)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary purpose of an endotracheal tube cuff in mechanically ventilated patients?',
    'answers': [
      'Maintain airway patency',
      'Enhance oxygenation',
      'Prevent aspiration',
      'Facilitate spontaneous breathing',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which condition may necessitate the use of pressure-controlled inverse ratio ventilation (PC-IRV)?',
    'answers': [
      'Pulmonary embolism',
      'Neurological injury',
      'Cardiac arrhythmia',
      'Severe bronchospasm',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In volume-controlled ventilation, what is the primary determinant of peak inspiratory pressure (PIP)?',
    'answers': ['Inspiratory time', 'Tidal volume', 'FiO2', 'Respiratory rate'],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What does the "apnea backup rate" setting on a ventilator control?',
    'answers': [
      'The rate at which alarms activate during apnea',
      'The maximum allowable FiO2 during apnea',
      'The minimum respiratory rate the ventilator will provide if the patient is apneic',
      'The rate of positive end-expiratory pressure (PEEP) during apnea',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which mode of ventilation is most appropriate for patients with acute exacerbations of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD)?',
    'answers': [
      'Pressure control ventilation',
      'Pressure support ventilation',
      'Volume control ventilation',
      'Pressure-regulated volume control (PRVC)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What does "auto-PEEP" refer to in the context of mechanical ventilation?',
    'answers': [
      'A type of positive end-expiratory pressure (PEEP)',
      'The maximum allowable tidal volume',
      'The patient\'s spontaneous breathing rate',
      'The amount of pressure exerted on the chest during CPR',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which parameter should be continuously monitored to prevent hypocapnia in a mechanically ventilated patient?',
    'answers': [
      'Oxygen saturation (SpO2)',
      'pH levels',
      'FiO2',
      'Tidal volume',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary purpose of the "pressure support" setting on a ventilator?',
    'answers': [
      'Prevent overventilation',
      'Deliver positive end-expiratory pressure (PEEP)',
      'Assist the patient\'s inspiratory effort',
      'Control the inspiratory time',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which type of mechanical ventilation is often used as a bridge to lung transplantation?',
    'answers': [
      'High-frequency oscillatory ventilation (HFOV)',
      'Pressure-controlled inverse ratio ventilation (PC-IRV)',
      'Volume control ventilation',
      'Airway pressure release ventilation (APRV)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In airway pressure release ventilation (APRV), what is the primary purpose of the "release phase"?',
    'answers': [
      'Deliver positive pressure to recruit collapsed alveoli',
      'Allow for exhalation and CO2 elimination',
      'Enhance oxygenation',
      'Facilitate spontaneous breathing',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which ventilator parameter is commonly adjusted to manage oxygenation in patients with severe acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS)?',
    'answers': [
      'Inspiratory pressure',
      'Tidal volume',
      'FiO2',
      'Inspiratory time',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In which scenario might "pressure-controlled inverse ratio ventilation" (PC-IRV) be used as a ventilation strategy?',
    'answers': [
      'To reduce the risk of barotrauma',
      'To minimize oxygenation',
      'To facilitate spontaneous breathing',
      'To manage severe ARDS',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary goal of "airway pressure release ventilation" (APRV) in patients with acute lung injury?',
    'answers': [
      'Increase tidal volume',
      'Maintain a constant FiO2',
      'Prevent hyperventilation',
      'Optimize oxygenation and ventilation',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which ventilator setting should be adjusted to decrease the patient\'s work of breathing during mechanical ventilation?',
    'answers': [
      'Inspiratory pressure',
      'Tidal volume',
      'Respiratory rate',
      'Positive end-expiratory pressure (PEEP)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which neurotransmitter is primarily associated with the regulation of mood and emotions?',
    'answers': ['Serotonin', 'Dopamine', 'Acetylcholine', 'GABA',],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary function of the Golgi apparatus within a cell?',
    'answers': [
      'Protein synthesis',
      'Lipid synthesis',
      'Packaging and modification of proteins',
      'ATP production',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following medications is classified as a loop diuretic?',
    'answers': [
      'Furosemide (Lasix)',
      'Metoprolol (Lopressor)',
      'Lisinopril (Zestril)',
      'Amlodipine (Norvasc)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the normal range for arterial blood pH in adults?',
    'answers': ['6.5 - 7.0', '7.35 - 7.45', '7.55 - 8.0', '8.5 - 9.0',],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which cranial nerve is responsible for both taste sensation on the anterior two-thirds of the tongue and salivary gland function?',
    'answers': [
      'Cranial nerve II (Optic)',
      'Cranial nerve V (Trigeminal)',
      'Cranial nerve VII (Facial)',
      'Cranial nerve X (Vagus)',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'In which type of shock does the body experience a severe allergic reaction leading to widespread vasodilation and decreased blood pressure?',
    'answers': [
      'Hypovolemic shock',
      'Neurogenic shock',
      'Anaphylactic shock',
      'Cardiogenic shock',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the primary role of the medulla oblongata in the brainstem?',
    'answers': [
      'Regulation of sleep-wake cycles',
      'Coordination of voluntary muscle movements',
      'Control of vital functions such as respiration and heart rate',
      'Memory storage and retrieval',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 2
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following is NOT a symptom of Addison\'s disease?',
    'answers': [
      'Hyperpigmentation',
      'Hypoglycemia',
      'Muscle weakness',
      'Hypotension',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which phase of the nursing process involves the systematic collection and analysis of data about a patient\'s health status?',
    'answers': ['Assessment', 'Planning', 'Implementation', 'Evaluation',],
    'correctIndex': 0
  },
  {
    'question':
    'What is the term for the excessive accumulation of cerebrospinal fluid within the ventricles of the brain?',
    'answers': [
      'Meningitis',
      'Hydrocephalus',
      'Encephalitis',
      'Cerebral edema',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 1
  },
  {
    'question':
    'Which of the following is an example of a positive feedback mechanism in the body?',
    'answers': [
      'Regulation of body temperature',
      'Blood glucose regulation',
      'Blood pressure regulation',
      'Uterine contractions during childbirth',
    ],
    'correctIndex': 3
  },
];